<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-12-11T14:07:25+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Twitter usage study</title><subtitle>small description about you will take you long</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Twitter usage allong the months</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/12/10/Twitter_usage_allong_month.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Twitter usage allong the months" /><published>2020-12-10T12:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-12-10T12:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/12/10/Twitter_usage_allong_month</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/12/10/Twitter_usage_allong_month.html">&lt;h4&gt;Abstract&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
This study aim to explore a sample of Twitter user data over multiple years to see whether user activity increase every year in some months and decrease some other. For exemple, is there more user activity in December than in July.
To so so we used the dataset provided by the authors of the paper we are trying to extend. 
We based this decision on the fact that about status, twitter api only allowed to grab recent tweets, and that the way of sampling realized in this paper is interesting and we did not wanted to denaturate it. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Results&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
We measured this activity via the number of tweets posts each months.
The histogram visualization permits to appreciate the results of this research.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/histo_ex1_month.png&quot; class=&quot;u-full-width&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;legend&gt;Distribution of Twitter user activity over the months for the years 2011, 2012 and 2013&lt;/legend&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Regarding this histogram we may conclude that users activity is always high in December, but we cannot status for others like October etc beacause the ratio change every year.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Kali group</name></author><summary type="html">Abstract This study aim to explore a sample of Twitter user data over multiple years to see whether user activity increase every year in some months and decrease some other. For exemple, is there more user activity in December than in July. To so so we used the dataset provided by the authors of the paper we are trying to extend. We based this decision on the fact that about status, twitter api only allowed to grab recent tweets, and that the way of sampling realized in this paper is interesting and we did not wanted to denaturate it. Results We measured this activity via the number of tweets posts each months. The histogram visualization permits to appreciate the results of this research. Distribution of Twitter user activity over the months for the years 2011, 2012 and 2013 Regarding this histogram we may conclude that users activity is always high in December, but we cannot status for others like October etc beacause the ratio change every year.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Find a model that fits user activity to predict account future</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/12/09/Model_of_user_activity.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Find a model that fits user activity to predict account future" /><published>2020-12-09T20:44:20+01:00</published><updated>2020-12-09T20:44:20+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/12/09/Model_of_user_activity</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/12/09/Model_of_user_activity.html">&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'Tom'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Kali group</name></author><summary type="html">You’ll find this post in your _posts directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run jekyll serve, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated. To add new posts, simply add a file in the _posts directory that follows the convention YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works. Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets: def print_hi(name) puts &quot;Hi, #{name}&quot; end print_hi('Tom') #=&amp;gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT. Check out the Jekyll docs for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at Jekyll’s GitHub repo. If you have questions, you can ask them on Jekyll Talk.</summary></entry></feed>